{"success": 1, "total": 2100, "result": [{"ID": "55fa6a5ce4b043d0caf2723b", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "1", "optionC": "0", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "-1", "type": "1", "optionA": "-2", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "Initialize integer i as 0, what's the value of i after the following operation?i += i > 0 ? i++ : i--;", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf2723c", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "5,4,3,2,1", "optionC": "1,2,5,4,3", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "3,5,1,4,2", "type": "1", "optionA": "1,2,3,4,5", "knowledge": "\u6811", "question": "Which of the follwing sequence(s) could not be a postorder tree walk result of a binary search tree?", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf2723d", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "None of the above", "optionC": "20", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "18", "type": "1", "optionA": "14", "knowledge": "C/C++ \u9012\u5f52", "question": "How many times is f() called when calculating f(10)?\nint f(int x) {\n    if(x <= 2)\n        return 1;\n    return f(x - 2) + f(x - 4) + 1;\n}", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf2723e", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "(1) Sort linked list(2) Array.", "optionC": "(1) Tree with linked list at leaves(2) Hash(10,000 buckets)", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "(1) Tree with linked list at leaves(2) Array.", "type": "1", "optionA": "(1) Tree with Hash(100 bucket) at leaves(2) Tree with linked list at leaves.", "knowledge": "\u6570\u7ec4 \u6811 \u94fe\u8868 \u54c8\u5e0c", "question": "Asume you have an object to describe customer data:{ ID\uff087 digit numeric\uff09 Family Name\uff08string\uff09 Account Balance\uff08currency\uff09 } If you have 500,000 Chinese customers records represented by instances of this object type , what set of data structures is best to get fast retrieval of customers (1) get IDs from Name and (2) get Name from ID?", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf2723f", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "O(n*n)", "optionC": "O(nlgn)", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "O(n)", "type": "1", "optionA": "O(lgn)", "knowledge": "\u6392\u5e8f", "question": "The best time complexity of quick sort algorithm is:", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27240", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "DES", "optionC": "RC4", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "RSA", "type": "1", "optionA": "MD5", "knowledge": "\u52a0\u5bc6\u548c\u5b89\u5168", "question": "Which of the following method(s) CANNOT be used for Text-encryption:", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27241", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "50", "optionC": "45", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "30", "type": "1", "optionA": "5", "knowledge": "\u7f16\u8bd1\u548c\u4f53\u7cfb\u7ed3\u6784", "question": "To speed up data access , we build cache system. In one system , The L1 cache access time is 5 ns , the L2 cache access time is 50 ns and the memory access time is 400 ns. The L1 cache miss rate is 50% , the L2 cache miss rate is 10%. The average data access time of this system is:", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27242", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "Many clustered index", "optionC": "clustered index and many non-clustered indexes", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "A clustered index", "type": "1", "optionA": "No indexes", "knowledge": "\u6570\u636e\u5e93", "question": "A table CANNOT have one or more of the following index configurations.", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27243", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "fastcal", "optionC": "pascal", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "stdcall", "type": "1", "optionA": "cdecl", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u4e0b\u9762\u54ea\u4e9b\u8c03\u7528\u8f6c\u6362\u652f\u6301\u53ef\u53d8\u957f\u5ea6\u53c2\u6570", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27244", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "A::f() A::f() const", "optionC": "A::f() B::f() const", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "B::f() A::f() const", "type": "1", "optionA": "B::f() B::f() const", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u4e0b\u9762\u7a0b\u5e8f\u6267\u884c\u7ed3\u679c:\nusing namespace std;\nclass A{\n    public:\n        virtual void f() { cout << \"A::f() \"; }\n        void f() const { cout << \"A::f() const \"; }\n};\nclass B : public A {\n    public:\n        void f() { cout << \"B::f() \"; }\n        void f() const { cout << \"B::f() const \"; }\n};\nvoid g(const A* a) {\n    a->f();\n}\nint main(int argc, char *argv[]) {\n    A* p = new B();\n    p->f();\n    g(p);\n    delete(p);\n    return 0;\n}", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27245", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u7ebf\u7a0b\u53ef\u4ee5\u66f4\u6539\u4ece\u5c5e\u7684\u8fdb\u7a0b", "optionC": "\u7ebf\u7a0b\u5fc5\u4ece\u5c5e\u4e8e\u4e00\u4e2a\u8fdb\u7a0b", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "\u8fdb\u7a0b\u6709\u81ea\u5df1\u7684\u6808\u7a7a\u95f4\uff0c\u800c\u7ebf\u7a0b\u53ea\u5171\u4eab\u7236\u8fdb\u7a0b\u7684\u6808\u7a7a\u95f4", "type": "1", "optionA": "\u64cd\u4f5c\u7cfb\u7edf\u7684\u4e00\u4e2a\u7a0b\u5e8f\u5fc5\u987b\u6709\u4e00\u4e2a\u8fdb\u7a0b\uff0c\u4f46\u662f\u4e0d\u5fc5\u987b\u6709\u4e00\u4e2a\u7ebf\u7a0b", "knowledge": "Windows \u64cd\u4f5c\u7cfb\u7edf", "question": "Windows \u4e0b\u8fdb\u7a0b\u548c\u7ebf\u7a0b\u7684\u63cf\u8ff0\uff0c\u54ea\u4e9b\u662f\u5bf9\u7684\uff1a", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27246", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "11 11", "optionC": "11 10", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "10 11", "type": "1", "optionA": "10 10", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u4e0b\u9762\u4ee3\u7801\u6bb5\u7684\u8fd0\u884c\u7ed3\u679c\uff08\u73af\u5883linux\u5e73\u53f0, g++\u7f16\u8bd1\u5668\uff09:\nint main() {\n    int x = 10;\n    int y = 10;\n    x = y = ++y;\n    printf(\"%d %d\", x, y);\n    return 0;\n}", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27247", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u6ea2\u51fa", "optionC": "2", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "6", "type": "1", "optionA": "9", "knowledge": "Java \u6570\u7ec4 C#", "question": "C# \u6216\u662f Java \u7a0b\u5e8f\u6bb5\u7684\u7ed3\u679c\uff1a int[][] array = new int[3][]{ new int[3]{5,6,2}, new int[5]{6,9,7,8,3}, new int[2]{3,2} }; array[2][2] \u8fd4\u56de\uff08\uff09", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27248", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "999", "optionC": "32", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "10", "type": "1", "optionA": "8", "knowledge": "\u667a\u529b\u9898", "question": "1000 \u4e2a\u74f6\u5b50\u4e2d\u6709\u4e00\u74f6\u6bd2\u836f\uff0c\u4e00\u53ea\u8001\u9f20\u5403\u5230\u6bd2\u836f\u4e00\u5468\u4e4b\u5185\u4f1a\u6b7b\uff0c\u5982\u679c\u8981\u5728\u4e00\u5468\u4e4b\u5185\u68c0\u6d4b\u51fa\u6709\u6bd2\u836f\u7684\u4e00\u74f6\uff0c\u95ee\u81f3\u5c11\u9700\u8981\u51e0\u53ea\u8001\u9f20\uff1f", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf27249", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "None of the above.", "optionC": "Changes to the parent process does not affect child processes.Multiple threads mar cause deadlock,while multiple processes  won't cause deadlock", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "Changes to the main thread(cancellation\uff0cpriority change\uff0cetc.) may affect the behavior of the other threads of the process;", "type": "1", "optionA": "Threads share the same address space of the parent process;Processes share the same address space of the parent process.", "knowledge": "\u64cd\u4f5c\u7cfb\u7edf", "question": "Which statement(s) is(are) correct about thread and process\uff1fSelect all that apply.", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf2724a", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "None of the above.", "optionC": "Port numbers below 1024 are called well-known ports and are reserved for standard services. For example,port 21 is reserved for FTP protocol, and port 25 is for SMTP protocol.", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "TCP supports multicasting.", "type": "1", "optionA": "TCP provides a way for applications to send encapsulated IP datagrams and send them without having to establish a connection.", "knowledge": "\u7f51\u7edc\u57fa\u7840", "question": "Which statement(s) below regarding TCP(Transmission Control Protocol) is(are) correct? Select all that apply.", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5de4b043d0caf2724b", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "const int *a; // a \u662f\u5e38\u6307\u9488", "optionC": "int const *a; // a \u6307\u5411\u5e38\u6570\u7684\u6307\u9488", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "int const a; // a \u662f\u5e38\u6570", "type": "1", "optionA": "const int a; // a \u662f\u5e38\u6570", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u4e0b\u9762\u8bf4\u6cd5\u9519\u8bef\u7684\u662f:", "title": "Microsoft-\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377A"}]}